etoolkit.com 2011-06-29

# eToolKit

**eToolKit Privacy Policy**

A unique identification reference is generated for each eToolKit installation. It is sent back to us each time the eToolKit communicates with our servers. 

Your bookmarks, MySafe entries, your email address and your eToolKit password are sent to our servers in case you have chosen to create account at etoolkit.com and use it for syncing your eToolKit. 

Use of Personal Information 

We process personal information collected through our servers and the eToolKit for the purposes of: 

(i) Dealing with your enquiries, requests and preferences;  
(ii) Providing you with information about updates and enhancements to our products and services;  
(iii) Personalizing your experience;  
(iv) Improving our software;

Disclosures 

We do not sell, trade or disclose your personal information to outside parties. However we may release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. 

Online Privacy Policy Only 

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected by the use of the eToolKit and our website and not to information collected offline. 

Your Consent 

By using our site and software, you consent to our online privacy policy. 

Changes of Privacy Policy 

We reserve the right, at our discretion, to update and change this Privacy Policy.  
The most recent version of this Privacy Policy is available at http://etoolkit.com/privacy.html.  
Privacy Policy can be changed by posting a new version without notice to you.  
Use of the eToolKit after such change constitutes acceptance of such changes.
